The End
Nope, didn't budge.
Not even a little bit.
Well, that punch has some
decent force behind it.
Is this guy for real?
He could give Nanami a run for his
money in terms of physical power,
though I suppose that's why It
makes sense that it's a sturdy veil.
We'll have to search for its
weak point and put a hole in it,
even if it's only for a second.
We can't get anywhere
without getting inside first.
Huh? Why not?
Why not?
Listen, this is a veil
that keeps sorcerers out.
It's a major barrier.
Barriers are all designed to
surround you and protect you, right?
Which fundamentally means that whoever
lowered this veil is inside it.
and being protected by it.
Yeah, but back in Harajuku...
I see what you mean.
So staying outside the Veil instead
of surrounding themselves with it?
Increases the risk of being
discovered and defeated!
but in return, the Veil's
strength increases.
It's a real Egg of Columbus
idea. Huh? Whose egg?
Though, man, they're completely
ignoring the fundamentals of barriers.
What a crazy idea.
Now I can see why the barrier didn't
break, despite how hard Yuji hit it.
According to that logic,
the veil's source should be somewhere
rather obvious to us, right?
The payoff for the increased risk of
being seen is a much more powerful veil.
Hmm.
Somewhere obvious?
That stands out?
Think the sorcerers will realize it.
This is the place that
stands out the most right
I assume so yeah but even
if they do realize it.
Yeah the lower poles are swarming
with those transfigured humans.
They won't be able to
climb up here fast enough.
A wire these are great.
I
wonder
do these bastards
know about the other fails.
Good just as planned so
this must be the source
of the veil yeah may may
told me it already has.
The barrier programmed
into the center of it it
just needs someone to pour
cursed energy into it.
To start its activation
which means as long as we
destroy those things we
can ignore the curse users.
Until later there were
three of them the veil
keeping sorcery sound is
still active where are?
With the remaining two?
What? With him?
Musiguro! Dismiss Nui!
Grandson yeah i know what to do granny
i'm leading some impressionable kids now.
So it's time for me to
earn some achievements here
as well then i can become
a first grade sorcerer too?
Fushiguro!
Where is he?
There.
I didn't see the moment of impact.
But his body's undamaged.
Even if he is a sorcerer, he still
plummeted from the City floor.
Get up now, you old trickster!
Good grief.
I mean, these youngsters today
have no pity for the elderly.
We can't waste time here.
It won't take us long.
Oh, it's a love song.
Now, let's go.
I love you, baby.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Why are you so insistent
on my recommendation?
You could easily become semi-first-grade
with your technique without a word for me.
Because I believe it's important
to do things the right way.
Especially with bloody
work like being a sorcerer.
But I'm not that bright, so sometimes
I don't know what the right way is.
So whenever I'm at a
loss, I think to myself...
What would Anonami do in this situation?
It wouldn't be right to become a
first grade without your approval.
Oh, would you like another drink?
A Mok Call.
Auspicious Beast Summon, number one.
Gojo.
It's homing?
The Seance Technique
Auspicious Beast Summon.
By hiding his face,
Eno can become a spiritual medium used to
manifest the powers of the
four auspicious beasts.
Granny, that was...
Yes, quite the coincidence.
Number two, Rika.
Nanami entrusted those two to me,
so I can't just leave them alone.
But it would be a bad idea
to leave these guys to them.
The best option is to kill them
fast and rejoin my underclassmen!
Adapt to the facts And maintain self
-control Cast aside Pride Fight him.
Matching pace with him takes more
effort than fighting the enemy.
Okay.
It's Adori! Hang on!
Don't worry, I'm good.
It's just a scratch.
So full of life, what promising futures?
Definitely worth killing.
Demon Dog's claws can
hurt even special grates.
I hit him with serious force, too.
Then how can it be?
It's not damaged at all.
I thought you told me this
wouldn't take us long.
No comment.
He's just as he seems.
Not all that strong.
But he's doing whatever it takes and
sacrificing himself to protect that old hag.
There's something more to them.
I should hurry up.
Their horrors changed.
We're all set, grandson.
Got it, Granny.
I won't let you!
Toji Zenin!
how is it grandson yeah it's
great granny better than any before
Happy birthday!
Your present's seeing me in my uniform.
Isn't it the most adorable
school uniform ever, Papa?
Woo!
I'm really glad I went
with Mori High. After all,
well if you're happy I'm happy
but you start out with that
much confidence you're gonna turn
out just like your mother huh?
do you hate mom or something?
no I don't hate her but she
did cheat on me
yeah I
know my poor Papa
I
killed
her I need
a corpse in order to transform
into someone I've summoned
although it didn't make any
difference to me she screamed
for her mother when she died?
sorry
it's
no good to me
looks like I I ripped it.
I'm begging you to please
let me out of here!
Shut up.
Why are you doing this?
What have I ever done
to you to deserve this?
My job is killing people.
So I need to really understand
how the human body works.
we were once free Jujutsu
sorcerers had their hands full
with the increasing number of
curses as long as we did things
right we could easily earn the
living without being tied down
by anything we curse users were
free to live and do as we pleased
satoru gojo yes the child born to the
gojo clan with the six
eyes a kid the total
bounty on his head is already over 100
million yen oh and this isn't a request
it's first come first serve
Thank you for waiting.
Cursed spirits have been
growing stronger over the years.
And in that instant I
understood exactly why!
Because of him, Satoru Gojo.
It was the same as when an insurmountable
track and field record
was suddenly broken?
The same as when figure
skaters started adding
more revolutions to their
jumps due to one athlete.
The balance of the world changed
when Satoru Gojo was born.
Quit looking at me, weakling.
We were free.
And in our later years...
That freedom was stolen from us!
Screw him!
I'll never stop trying
to get our freedom back.
I'll tremble over the weekend
to the very day I die.
This is fun.
Seriously, what is with this guy?
It's not even about him
being tough anymore.
It's almost certainly the
result of his technique.
Damage nullification?
No.
Hey!
Satoru Gojo is here in Shibuya!
Leave the Veil Foundations
and run while you can!
What a lousy bluff that is.
Gojo has been sealed.
You were the one shouting
from the rooftop so loudly.
That's why we're out here
having fun, you know?
If Gojo was still active,
we'd be at home sleeping.
I knew it.
There's no way he could be Gojo.
Fushiguro, you suck at lying.
That means this guy's technique can't
be something as grand as nullification.
That's okay.
It's okay? Shut up.
If you don't want to fight anymore,
just tell me and I'll kill you.
Here he comes.
Yeah.
Rabbit escape!
Fall back.
I finally figured out his technique.
Transformation through seance?
That head is a medium?
No, that's not the problem here.
What's up with him?
Is he some famous sorcerer?
I can tell by his stance.
He's Hall strong!
Number four, Ryu!
The type of Shikigami that
distracts with numbers.
So they're planning to launch a lethal
attack from the cover of these hairs, huh?
They're gone.
Did they run away?
Max Elephant!
Hey what the hell is this appearing
and disappearing what are you restless
if you're a man be clear and decisive
not my style but I'll let my friend know
What is with this brat's incredible power?
He's giving me chills.
For now, just keep attacking.
This guy's engine is getting
pretty revved up too.
A finishing blow.
My technique is inverse.
While activated, the stronger the
attacks, the weaker they feel.
And the weaker the attacks,
the stronger they become.
Not one person has ever
managed to dodge my
counterattack after landing
their finishing blow.
The more serious you two get, the
less chance you have against me.
I finally figured out his technique. Huh?
I'm pretty sure it's an inverse technique.
My out-of-sync attack landed more
effectively than your direct one.
Rabbit escape isn't meant for offense,
but he didn't try to immediately
break through once he was surrounded.
I think the fact that
he's fine after being
beaten into the ground
also supports my theory.
So, we can defeat him
with a forehead flick?
No, the attack can't be too weak.
If it was just pure inversion of force,
activating it in something as simple
as a light breeze would kill him.
Since that isn't happening, there must be
an upper and lower limit to his inversion.
And even with it activated,
he countered our attacks
and used cursed energy
for protection from the
effects of our techniques.
That makes sense.
That also explains why he's
afraid of an anomaly like Gojo.
His technique's probably a bad match
against complicated techniques.
Which means we need to strike together.
We'll hit him with a powerful
attack and a weaker one.
At the same time!
Right, but we don't want him to realize
we've figured out his technique.
So we'll keep going at full power and
make a show of our crazy strength.
I'll start with a weak blow from Game.
Then we'll pummel him with a rush.
Wait.
Did they figure it out?
But still.
No goody for you.
You figured out my technique.
Don't get cocky, you BRATS!
He stopped it.
He killed his momentum for just a moment.
You're surprisingly adept, you know that?
Really?
I'll be right back.
I want you to believe in yourself, right?
I want you to believe in yourself.
Just be by yourself.
And give it more than once?
Give it more than once!